I) ZFIN: http://zfin.org/
1 Yes
2 Gene Ontology and Anatmical Ontology
3 ZFIn has help wiki, newsgroup, how to ingest ontologized data. For Ontologies: Normal AO & GO support. Page with links to connect to zeprafish anatomy ontology


II) Ontobee: www.ontobee.org
1 Yes
2 Site uses 120 different ontologies. All in OBO foundry
3 Everything in OBO Foundry. Direct links to ontology tools. SPARQL term queries. 


III) OLS: http://www.ebi.ac.uk/ontology-lookup/
1 Yes
2 85 molecular -ish databases
3 Workshops, digital developer resources, software and data downfall


IV) Morphbank: http://morphbank.net
1 No. Seems to be reliant on non-ontology metadata to explore content. 
4 Would have semantic search capability, ability to reason compare  over data

V) Bioportal: bioportal.bioontology.org
1 Yes
2 349 biological ontologies
3 Contact info for all ontologies, ability to submit suggested terms. Find terms. Create new bioportal ontologies, discuss ontologies among community


VI) http://www.virtualflybrain.org
1 Yes
2 Anatomy Ontology
3 Not that we can see, other than normal AO support


VII) http://datadryad.org/
1 No
4 Maybe, but not obviously. They allow data from all disciplines, so detailed ontologies might be overkill. However, if they ontologized data according to high-level ontologies, then the data would be sharable across repositories. 